Missing threat modeling matters because applications often enforce identity, access,
data handling, business workflows, and service integrations.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Weak architecture matters because applications often enforce identity, access,
data handling, business workflows, and service integrations.
Unsafe workflows matters because applications often enforce identity, access,
Business logic flaws matters because applications often enforce identity, access,
data handling, business workflows, and service integrations.
Threat modeling Secure SDLC Security architecture reviews Selected CIS Controls mappings
for this topic include Control 16 - Application Software Security;
Control 14 - Security Awareness & Skills Training;
16.1 - Establish secure application development process; 16.4 - Threat modeling;
14.1 - Establish security awareness program.